<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP-taak_CaeyersBert</title>
    <link>http://bert-caeyers.github.io/categories/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP-taak_CaeyersBert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 14:50:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://bert-caeyers.github.io/categories/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-autobiography</title>
      <link>http://bert-caeyers.github.io/post/English-Profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 14:50:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bert-caeyers.github.io/post/English-Profile/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:f1de07b44e20f124b6627c2ecaf1f26d&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m the number one knowledge book of games. My nickname is as you can guess  ‘gaming bible’. I’m 17 years old. I’m a student of the Immaculata institute because there I can study informatics and learn more about computers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first experience with IT was with the computer at home. I played the best game I ever played then. The game was called ‘pinball’. At that time I was 7 years old I think. I thought it was fantastic because you had a screen and you could move something on it. It was just an amazing experience. There was actually nothing that roused my interest it was just that we had a pc and I wanted to do something on it. My mom said I could play on it for about30 minutes so I enjoyed it. I mostly visited the site ‘funnygames’ on the internet. But I just mostly didn’t go on the internet and just played pinball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the moment IT actually means a lot because almost everything in our lives has informatics in it. But if you asking me 7 years ago I would&amp;rsquo;ve said almost ‘nothing’. That is because the IT world is growing really fast. In a normal day now I spend like 2 hours on the computer, mostly watching series and listening to music. Sometimes I game but my parents forbid it on schooldays. In gaming I hav not achieved a lot but I have already  assembled 5 computers and I have made 2 networks. That’s all. I just think it’s fantastic if you spend 3 hours on building the pc and then you see that it works. That’s just an amazing feeling. It’s also really nice to see the person you made the pc for happy with his pc. I actually don’t see myself as an expert. That’s because experts have been searching everything around the subject and work on it every day. I’m just someone who knows a lot about it but nothing more. And I think I can still develop in knowing more about building pcs and pc components. Because if you are interested in something, you want to know everything about it. And I&amp;rsquo;m surely interested in pcs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really would like to have a shop of pc components where I also build computers. Just because I&amp;rsquo;m interested in that. And they always say you become happier when you like to do your job. It’s actually kind of my dream job right now. There are also not a lot of shops in Belgium like this so that’s really good. And I don’t really have other aspirations. Maybe later this year I’m going to but at the moment I don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../Afbeeldingen/IT-autobiography2.png&#34; alt=&#34;afbeelding1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do think my pc and IT have  become an important part of my life. I don’t think I can’t live without them. But I do think I spend a lot of time on a pc. Not only in school but also in my spare time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review</title>
      <link>http://bert-caeyers.github.io/post/Review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 14:50:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bert-caeyers.github.io/post/Review/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;driver-genius:34ebcfd1cfa3321b387d6c584f68cba4&#34;&gt;Driver Genius&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to review the online tool Driver Genius today. Driver Genius is a program that helps you keep track of your Windows drivers. You can use it for every pc that has a Windows operating system. You are probably asking yourself what drivers are, drivers are components of a computer that you connect with your motherboard. They can be internal but also peripheral like a mouse / computer screen  but also a cpu or gpu. These drivers are needed so the components are compatible with your operating system (windows). You could look them up by brand but that&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work. I used this tool during my apprenticeship for a lot of things but mostly for cleaning up computers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why is this tool so useful? Well the most common problems with pcs are drivers that are not up-to-date. This tool keeps all the drivers that are needed for your pc up-to-date. What&amp;rsquo;s good about this, is that it’s with one tool so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to search every driver by brand. This saves you a lot of time and is really easy to use. The tool works on every pc that runs Windows. You also have other tools like this one Driver Support or Smart Driver Updater. But I can&amp;rsquo;t give my opinion about the other ones because I only used Driver Genius. So how does the tool begins his work. It starts by searching for the different drivers. When it has found all the drivers it searches if the drivers must be updated. After this it asks you if it can install all the updates of the drivers. You then just click &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; and the tool starts installing all the updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I think is good about this tool is that it&amp;rsquo;s really easy to use. Everybody can use it because you just need to run the program and then click on two buttons. What&amp;rsquo;s also really useful is that the tool has a big unique database of all the drivers. So if you want you can search them yourself. This is also the strongest point pointed out by the review I read. Driver Genius is the only tool for drivers that has this. What&amp;rsquo;s also really good is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about the third party developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course it doesn&amp;rsquo;t only have good features. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a bit too expensive if you just want to use it for your home pc. I also read other reviews and they said it only found half of the updates. The most not found updates were peripheral. But I have to disagree with this negative point because when I used it I always found all the updates. Over the two weeks I used it I didn&amp;rsquo;t find two updates. So I think it&amp;rsquo;s a really good tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion:34ebcfd1cfa3321b387d6c584f68cba4&#34;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really positive about this tool because it&amp;rsquo;s easy to use. It also found most of the updates when I used it. The tool also has a really nice interface and the database is so helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s mostly good for big companies or companies with a lot of pcs. This is because like I already said most of the pc problems are with drivers that are not up to date and a lot of companies depend on their computers nowadays. So if that problem is solved that would be fantastic for companies and for these companies it&amp;rsquo;s only a small price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t advise small companies or people at home to use it, because paying so much for just three computers is not worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>